Do you need to read your Bible?
I do. I know better than you, trust me.
Call me any pasuk, I'll tell you.
So tell me where ruach and defesh are,
where fruits have ruach and defesh.
It's defined ruach.
Ruach?
It's defined in the scripture.
Ruach means something that has a spirit.
Anything that moves, anything that moves, everything.
That also has a living ruach.
The breath of life.
Trees also have like ruach.
You got plenty of footage already, man.
You can do that all you want.
I'll give you a mimer.
Do you want to let a mimer with me?
When you take the fruit off of a tree,
the tree continues to live and grows more trees.
Right, but the apple doesn't.
That apple doesn't.
But if you take an apple off, it doesn't.
And you're eating an apple, not eating the tree.
No, the seed. The seed lives on.
But if you swallow the seed, it's not growing.
It grows after you pass through your system.
So I'm going to eat the chicken, and it'll continue growing.
It'll continue growing, he says.
The chicken grows after it ever is dead.
It'll grow in me, yeah.
I'm going to grow.
It grows in you.
I'm going to do good stuff.
There's blood on his face, man.
Right.
Without spilling blood in the street.
Stand there all you want.
Yeah, it's beautiful.
I'm saying that we're killing it.
We're killing it like it's not going away.
I told them, it's the veggies.
We have veggies.
We don't care about that.
They're vegan.
They eat fruits.
Which prophets? Tell me. Which prophets? Maybe go and tell them. Go get a bone. The prophets of the scripture of the Tanakh. Jeremiah. How do you bring a sacrifice? You can't kill the animal when you bring a sacrifice.
Do you know Hebrew? Yeah, they all bring. They bring lambs, they bring oxen. Kill them all the time.
Chesed. Chesed to God. God needs the kindness if you bring the sacrifice so often.
What does define murder? That's what you think. I think it's kindness.
Oh look, there's two sides of the fence. You're on that side, I'm on this side.
Wait, Alou, Alou.
Look at that. Look at that. What do you think about that?
It's saying in the Bible, it never speaks about bringing animals to the sacrificial of us, never.
The entire Leviticus, every single book, every single chapter of it speaks about it.
You're going to listen to the prophet, you're going to listen to the prophet, you're going to listen to God.
If God has something in the Bible, you're going to listen to that of the prophet.
So you're going to translate one prophet in one prophet.
Jeremiah said the Torah was falsified.
I know there's a whole book of the Bible, a whole book of the God's writings.
Jeremiah said god did not command that time.
I know you're not smart enough.
Dude, forget the scriptures, open your eyes.
You think God wants this?
I'm enjoying it.
Don't leave for your time.
That's what they want out of you.
You want to come here, they want to take you.
Open your eyes, man.
You guys speak whatever.
You're covered in blood.
I know, it's good.
You want some?
No, I do not.
Well, if a chicken gets you, Daddy, what would happen?
Jeremiah said your skirts are stained with blood.
It's a den of paris, a den of murder.
God's house is meant to be a house of prayer, not murder.
Look at you, you're dropping chickens on the ground.
This isn't a house, man.
It's murder, it's murder.
What did it do for you?
What did you want me here defending you?
We don't stay here, we don't stay here.